soundest.com 2016-04-13

# Privacy Policy - eCommerce email marketing | Soundest

| Soundest (the "Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit the Company's Web sites and individuals who register to use the Services as defined below. This Privacy Policy describes the Company's privacy practices in relation to the use of the Company's Web sites and the related applications and services offered by Soundest under various brands, and which applications and services are accessible via the Company Web sites listed below (the "Services").  
---|---  
1. | Websites Covered  
|  This Privacy Policy covers the information practices of Web sites that link to this Privacy Policy, including www.soundest.com and [www.soundest.net](https://soundest.net/) and local variations (collectively referred to as "the Company's Web sites"). This Privacy Policy covers the information practices of Web sites that link to this Privacy Policy, including www.soundest.com and [www.soundest.net](https://app.soundest.com/) and local variations (collectively referred to as "the Company's Web sites").   
| The Company's Web sites may contain links to other Web sites. The information practices or the content of such other Web sites are governed by the privacy statements of such other Web sites.  
2. | Information collected  
| The Company collects individually identifiable information ("Personal Information") from individuals who visit the Company's Web site ("Web Site Visitors") and individuals who register to use the Services ("Customers").  
| When expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the Services or registering to use the Services, the Company requires you to provide the Company with personal contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, and email address ("Required Contact Information").  
| When purchasing the Services, the Company may require you to provide the Company with financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, and the number of employees within the organization that will be using the Services ("Billing Information").  
| Required Contact Information, Billing Information, and optional information about Customers are referred to collectively as "Data About Customers".  
| As you navigate the Company's Web sites, Company may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and Web beacons ("Web Site Navigational Information"). Web Site Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, geolocation and the actions you take on the Company's Web sites (such as the Web pages viewed and the links clicked).  
| When Customer uploads or creates an email distribution list or put together an email campaign via Company's Services, the Company has access to the data on your list and the information in your campaign.  
| When Customer sends emails to his recipients, the Company always tracks who opened the emails and who clicked on any of the hyperlinks included. This information is used to measure and report the performance of email campaigns, and to improve Services.  
| The Company may obtain additional information about Customer's e-mail recipients by using recipient's email address, or other information, to directly, or through one or more services, search over the internet, or elsewhere. The Company thereby obtain information that appears to be related to such email address or other information, such as a name, age and participation in social media websites ("Supplemental Member Information").  
3. | Subscriber lists, Campaign content and Campaign reports  
| The Company ensures that all subscriber lists, email content and reports remain private and confidential. The Company may scan the content of your campaigns to ensure it complies with the Company's Terms of Use.  
| The Company will not sell, rent, loan or invite external access to a customer's contact lists. Nor will Company themselves use customer's contact lists for any purpose.  
4. | Use of information collected  
| The Company uses Data About Customers to perform the services requested. For example, if you fill out a "Contact Me" Web form, the Company will use the information provided to contact you about your interest in the Services.  
| The Company may also use Data About Customers for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in the Services and to send you information regarding the Company, its affiliates, and its partners, such as information about promotions or events.  
| The Company may use Data About Customers to send System Alert Messages to let you know about temporary or permanent changes to our Services including planned outages, new features offered, version updates, point releases, major releases, abuse warnings, changes to our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy and possibly other documents and agreements.  
| The Company may use Data About Customers to help enforce compliance with our Terms of Use, Anti-Spam Policy and applicable law including, but not limited to, helping to create white lists and black lists, to develop and test algorithms, heuristics and other methods and tools for detecting violations and to apply those methods and tools.  
| The Company uses Data About Customers to provide customer support and obtain feedback.  
| The Company uses Billing Information solely to check the financial qualifications and collect payment for the Services.  
| The Company uses Web Site Navigational Information to operate and improve the Company's Web sites. The Company may also use Web Site Navigational Information alone or in combination with Data About Customers to provide personalized information about the Company and the Services. Company may use both Data About Customers and Web Site Navigational Information to enforce the Company's Web site policies, or to protect the Company's rights and intellectual property or the rights of others using the Company's Web sites or the Services.  
5. | Sharing of information collected  
| The Company may share Data About Customers with the Company's contracted service providers so that these service providers can provide services on the Company's behalf. Company may also share Data About Customers with the Company's service providers to ensure the quality of information provided. Unless described in this Privacy Policy, Company does not share, sell, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes.  
| The Company may use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use Billing Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on the Company's behalf.  
| The Company reserves the right to use or disclose information provided if required by law or if the Company reasonably believes that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the Company's rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.  
6. | Correcting and updating you information  
| The Company does it's best to keep Customer's data accurate and up-to-date to the extent that Customer provides the Company with the information the Company require to do that. If Customer's data changes (including, but not limited to, a change in Customer's email address) then Customer is responsible for notifying Company of those changes so that Company can keep Customer's records up-to-date.  
| The Company will give Customer access to any of his Personal Information that the Company holds about him/her within 30 days of any request Customermakesfor such information. The Companymay charge for providing this information to Customer, as permitted by applicable law.  
| Customers may update or change their registration information by editing their user or organization record. To update a user profile, please login to the applicable Services with your Soundest Connect username and password and edit your user settings, or send your request to [info@soundest.com](mailto:info@soundest.com). To update an organization's information, please send your request to [info@soundest.com](mailto:info@soundest.com).  
7. | Security  
| The Company takes precautions, including administrative, technical, and physical measures – to help safeguard Data About Customers against loss, theft, and misuse as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.  
| Service users are solely responsible for protecting their passwords, limiting access to their computers, and signing out of the Services after their sessions.  
| The Company will notify Customer, as soon as possible, if a breach in security results in an unauthorized intrusion into Company's system which materially affects Customer or people on Customer's databases, and will subsequently report the corrective action taken in response to the intrusion.  
8. | Changes to this Privacy Policy  
| The Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy. The Company will provide notification of the material changes to this Privacy Statement through the Company's Web sites and via e-mail if permission is given by Customer to be e-mailed at least thirty (30) days prior to the change taking effect.  
9. | Data Protection Basis  
| According to resolution 2R-3202 issued on October 10th of 2011 (based on Republic of Lithuania Government resolution no. 262 issued on February 20th of 2002) The Company is notified as a "data controller" in respect of personal data about Lithuanian clients about whom the Company collects personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Under Republic of Lithuania law, the Company is a "data controller" in respect of the personal data about Company's Lithuanian Customers but not in respect of personal data about people on Customer's databases and recipient's lists (where we act as a "data processor").  
10. | Contacts  
| If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to report privacy abuse, please contact us:  
Soundest LLC  
Attn. Legal department, Saviciaus 13, Vilnius, Lithuania   
Phone +370-686-99430
